Punch is incoming! Two in a row!
His ice breath is next!
Coming up in three, two, one, now!
Now it's our turn! Wow!
I was always in the light of the night
I was not even in the sky I was not able
to reach my feet I was not able to reach
the sky I was not able to reach the sky
Do naiyume ka sa ne te Izu
aru Cait no nai ano hikari wo
Oh, give it for my way
Attack batter, it's changing!
Stay sharp! Oh my god. Kazuto!
There's only three clear spots left.
Can't you use that skill
connector thingy you used before?
He's still got two bars
left on his HP gauge.
Skill connect won't even put a dent in it.
Watch out!
Ice breath coming up!
Oh no, the buff!
Hazard, don't wait!
Get out of there!
Xenon!
Keep him busy for a few!
Swordsman, if we continue this course
of action, we will not defeat Thrymmer.
There is but one hope now.
Somewhere in this room,
hidden in the plunder,
you will find the treasure
of my people. I'm on it.
Tell me what it looks
like and I'll grab it.
It is about yea big.
It is a hammer made of gold.
Wait, it's a hammer?
Hey, Kazuto, you can find it using a
lightning skill! Lightning? Really?
There it is.
Freya! Chance!
It flows into me.
Freya?
Through me, it overflows.
No!
Freya?
She's a...
A friggin' dude!
Oh, he's Thor, the god of thunder.
Hmm?
You despicable giant!
Your treachery and deceit
has come to an end,
and now you shall pay
for stealing Mjolnir!
I shall make you pay for deceiving
me, you miserable excuse of a god!
I shall rip that beard from your face
and send your buddy back to Asgard!
Thor's pulling aggro from Thrymmer.
Let's attack while we can.
Here we go, guys! Hit him
hard! Don't hold back!
Use all your sword skills!
This is it!
Return to your abyss, King of the Diets!
AVAILABLE NOW Revel in
your victory, insects!
But take heed if you put your
faith in the dogs of Aesir!
You have my gratitude,
brave fairy warriors.
Thanks to you, my treasure has been
returned and my disgrace avenged.
Now then, I must reward you.
That is Mjolnir, the lightning hammer.
Use it in noble battles.
Farewell, my champions.
Congrats, pal.
You got a legendary weapon.
Yeah, but it's a hammer.
I don't got no hammer skills.
The room's moving!
Wait, is it floating?
Hey, Kazucho?
I don't think this quest is over yet. Huh?
Good fairies, infiltrate Thrymheim.
Remove Excalibur from its
plinth and save my realm.
Look at the medallion.
It's all black except
for that one clear spot.
Daddy!
A stairway leading down has just
appeared behind the throne! Seriously?
Let's go!
System command!
Generate object!
ID Excalibur!
Long time no see.
You got it, Kirito!
Come on, pull harder!
Put your back into it!
Don't give up, Daddy!
You can do it!
I know you can do it!
Don't keep pulling!
Oh, crap.
It's breaking up!
Daddy!
Thrymheim is collapsing!
We have to leave here now!
I know, I know!
Alright!
Looks like it's up to me to save the day!
Time for some Olympic grade high jumping!
Ow!
We're so screwed.
Leafa, how much time we got?
We made it!
Thank God!
Yeah.
Looks like I can't claim Excalibur
unless the quest is cleared.
Did you hear that? Huh?
There it is again.
Tonki!
We're saved!
Hurry, guys.
Hop on his back.
We're running out of time.
Yeah, I know.
Wish it wasn't so high up. Go on. Jump!
Hey, Donkey.
Thanks for saving my ass.
I guess you're still too heavy for me.
Daddy?
Seriously, stupid cardinal system.
That's about 200 meters.
Eku, Ski-Ta, Aftal, Eil
You gotta be kidding?
Heavy!
C! C! C! C!
C-9!
That was awesome!
Don't look at me like that.
You can have it.
Here. Thanks!
You're the best!
I'll give it to you,
but with one condition.
You gotta promise me.
Every time you dry, you have
to think about me, okay?
Well, well.
The chick magnet's got another girl's...
You got it.
I'll think about you every time I try it.
Thanks a lot.
You're more than welcome.
Man, this sucks.
We only got to do one quest in
it, and now it's gone for good.
I know.
It seems like such a waste.
Look at that, it's sprouting!
It's so warm.
So warm.
He's happy.
I'm happy, too.
Isn't this great, Tonki?
Look, all your friends have
come to say hi. You see them?
They're all waving.
You're a popular guy.
He removed Excalibur from its plinth.
The quest has been completed.
Now that the sword which
slices wood and iron is secure,
Jotunheim can return to its former glory.
It is all thanks to you and your bravery.
My younger sisters would also like to
express their gratitude towards you.
My name is Berdandi.
Thank you,
oh brave fairy warriors, to think I
can gaze upon a green Jotunheim again.
Oh, it's like a dream.
And my name is Sculpt.
You have my thanks and respect.
My gift to you shall be the Holy Sword.
Yes!
Thank you, noble fairies.
Until we meet again.
We finally cleared it.
Um, excuse me, Lady Skolt?
Can I get your number?
Right now, I respect you
more than ever, Klein.
You can be a dork, but you got heart.
How's that, Yui?
I can see perfectly, Daddy!
And I can hear, too!
Cool, but what is it?
I'm turning real-time footage
of the cafe into mock 3D images.
Okay, try moving, but take it slow.
Okay!
If it's working right, Huey should
feel like she's flying around the room.
I get it.
That camera and its mic are
acting like Huey's eyes and ears.
Gotta hand it to you,
that's pretty clever.
Kazuto's taking a class called Mecho...
Mecha-something.
It's mechatronics.
Like I was saying, he's
taking this Mecha-thing class.
He has to do a project, so
we came up with this idea.
But if you ask me, he's
just doing it for Yui.
You're spoiling me, Daddy!
Nice job, guys!
We got the Holy Sword Excalibur
and Mjolnir, the lightning hammer!
Congrats to 2025!
To us!
Hey, I was wondering, why did they
call it Excalibur in the game? Huh?
What do you mean, why?
Well,
usually in the fantasy
books and comics I've read,
it's always called
Caliburn, not Excalibur.
Oh, I don't know. No way!
You don't seem like someone
who'd be a fan of fantasy books.
When I was in middle school, I
pretty much lived at the library.
I spent all my time there
reading books about King Arthur.
Every one of them referred
to it as Caliburn.
Actually, didn't the sword go by a lot of
different names in most of those legends?
Depending on which Celtic language.
But the word caliber is cool because it's
what you call the
diameter of a gun barrel.
And it's also how you describe the
quality of a person's character.
Thanks for the lesson, Teach.
Sorry if I got carried away there.
So basically what you're saying is,
whoever owns Excalibur has to be someone
who's an exceptional person. Huh? Who is?
You mean Kirito?
Yeah, of course. Duh.
In fact, he's so exceptional,
he wouldn't think twice about paying for
dinner with some of that
crazy money he made,
right?
Yeah, I was saving it for a
surprise, but yeah, totally.
This dinner's on me.
Next time, The Forest House.